# JAMES OSORIO FLOREZ

# ANALISIS Y DESARROLLO DE SISTEMAS DE INFORMACIÓN

## **Profile**

I like to develop systems of information, create solutions, and face problems that help me be a better developer.

Experience developing custom web applications and macros in Excel.

- Portfolio: https://ossrezz.me/
- GitHub: github.com/OssRezz
- Email: OssRezz.13@gmail.com
- LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/ossrezz/
- Cellphone: +57-319 327 0780

# **Technologies**

- PHP
- JavaScript
- React
- Vba excel
- Bootstrap
- HTML

- Laravel
- JQuery
- React Native
- Git
- MySQL
- Css

## Education

ANÁLISIS Y DESARROLLO DE SISTEMAS DE INFORMACIÓN

SENA (Servicio Nacional De Aprendizaje) 1 October 2019 - 1 October 2021

# **Experience**

#### Clase De Excel S.A.S



Cra. 43A #5a-31, El Poblado, Medellín, Antioquia

https://clasedeexcel.com/

Analista y desarrollador de sistemas de información, macros en Excel

Abril 2022 - Actualidad

Octubre 2021 - Abril 2022



## Galaxia Seguridad Ltda.

Av. Nutibara #72-85, Laureles, Medellín, Antioquia

https://galaxiaseguridad.net/contacto/

Analista y desarrollador de sistemas de información

#### Flores Isabelita S.A.S



Vda. el Yarumo, La Ceja, Antioquia https://floresisabelita.falconfarms.com.co/

Analista y desarrollador de sistemas de información

Abril 2021 - Septiembre 2021

# **Projects**

The projects listed below are some of the ones developed by me from 0 to production in my past work experiences.

You can see more information like images, videos, GitHub repositories, and links to demos in my portoflio.

### Latinco

#### **Description**

Latinco is a company that is part of the execution of big projects involving highway interconnection in Colombia. The objective of the application is to evade human mistakes and generate reports for the different areas of the company. This process was done on Excel.

The application consumes an ERP and allows the users to manage the administrative processes of the company.

- ->Manage inability and inability extensions
- ->Personal entry control with follow-up on the medic process and reference investigations
- -> Cash flow
- ->Laboral cost

## **Technologies**

Developed in the framework of PHP Laravel, with the database MySQL, JavaScript and Ajax to render content in real time and interact with the user, Bootstrap 5 for the styles and design of the page.

**Experience in:** 



Clase De Excel S.A.S

# **GymPlus**

## **Description**

GymPlus is a company with four headquarters in the city of Medellin, Antioquia. The objective of the application is to allow users to reserve a class of spinning(cycling).

The application allows management:

- -> Bicycles maps of headquarters
- -> Spinning classes
- -> Teachers
- -> Reserves
- -> Asistences
- -> Users with active plans (Excel spreadsheet generated from another application)

#### **Technologies**

An application created using the PHP Laravel framework. The technologies implemented are HTML, Boostrap 5 for the styles and layout, pure JavaScript and Ajax to interact with the actions of the user. For database MySQL

Experience in:



Clase De Excel S.A.S

# Galaxia Seguridad ERP

#### **Description**

Galaxia Seguridad Ltda is a security company with different services. The objective of this project is to integrate every process of the company into an ERP.

#### Commercial module

- -> Manage companies
- -> Manage headquarters
- -> Managing newly acquired positions and services
- -> Provider of security services

#### **Human Resources Module**

- -> Manage employees
- -> Managed employees' binary files

## Risk Analysis Module

- -> Perimeter location, number of support groups (police, hospitals, armed forces)
- -> Vulnerability rating (Lighting, infrastructure, historical context..etc)
- -> Heat map with a risk rating based on impact and probability
- -> Risk treatments and proposals to improve treatment.
- -> Recommendations from the executive in charge of analyzing and monitoring

#### **Communications Module**

-> PQRS System

#### **Technologies**

Application created with the programming language PHP with the architectural pattern MVC. The technologies implemented are HTML and Bootstrap 5 for the styles and layout of the page. JavaScript and Ajax to interact with the users' actions. We use Amazon Web Service \$3 to store images, binary files and MySQL for the database.

**Experience in:** 



🛕 Galaxia Seguridad Ltda.

## Control of access

## **Description**

Galaxia Seguridad Ltda. is a security company with various national (Colombia) services. The goal of this project is to provide an application for access control as a service.

- -> Parameterization by company
- -> Parameterization of zones (pools, soccer fields, food zones, etc.)
- -> Persona type parameterization (provider, employee, visitor, domiciliario, etc.)
- -> Type of origin (potential visitor destinations)
- -> Attachments (Arma, computers, car plates)
- -> Register of Visitants
- -> Give access to visitors.

# **Technologies**

The application was developed in the programming language PHP with the architectural pattern MVC. The technologies implemented are HTML, Bootstrap 4 for styles and layoud. JQuery to send and receive information from the controllers. MySQL for database.

**Experience in:** 



🛕 Galaxia Seguridad Ltda.